<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Map on XXL Steve</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/categories/map/</link><description>Recent content in Map on XXL Steve</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xxlsteve.net/categories/map/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trash Collectors! #TeamSeas</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/trash-collectors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/trash-collectors/</guid><description>Help clean the ocean by collecting trash in Trash Collectors! A fun map to compete with friends and support MrBeast&amp;rsquo;s and Mark Rober&amp;rsquo;s #TeamSeas campaign! Collect trash, feed turtles and buy various powerups joined with MrBeast&amp;rsquo;s outro song music in noteblocks!
What is Team Seas?
#TeamSeas is a global campaign to raise $30 million to remove 30 million pounds of plastic and trash from our ocean, rivers and beaches before 2022, led by Mark Rober and Jimmy (MrBeast)!</description></item><item><title>French Slap</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/french-slap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/french-slap/</guid><description>French Slap is a game where the goal is to knock the players off the map. Last player alive wins! But this map is in a &amp;ldquo;typically-French&amp;rdquo; theme/style, and with little twists!
Additions:
Baguette - enchanted with Knockback 2, use it to hit players off the map! Cheese Power - right-click on PC or long-tap on mobile to trigger it, and you will get a levitation effect for 1 second! Power-up - it will randomly spawn in the game.</description></item><item><title>A Little Simple Spleef Game</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/spleef/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/spleef/</guid><description>Just a little, simple Spleef game. This map contains 2 arenas; the first with 2 layers and the second with 3 layers, and 2 gamemodes (Classic Spleef &amp;amp; Snowball Spleef).
How to Play:
Your goal is to break the block under the other players to make them fall. At the final layer they will fall to the void and die! Last player alive wins.
Gamemodes:
Classic Spleef:
Normal Spleef.
Snowball Spleef:</description></item><item><title>Death Swap (2 Players Only)</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/death-swap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/death-swap/</guid><description>⚠️ Warning: this is my first map, therefore it is very buggy and&amp;hellip; bad. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to play Death Swap, use this addon instead: Scommander&amp;rsquo;s Death Swap Ultimate ⚠️
Welcome to Death Swap, a mini-game of trapping your friend! When the game starts, you have 8 minutes to gather resources. Then the swapping will begin! You and your friend will swap places! The goal is to kill your opponent! By United Noobs.</description></item></channel></rss>