<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v1.16 on XXL Steve</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/tags/v1.16/</link><description>Recent content in v1.16 on XXL Steve</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xxlsteve.net/tags/v1.16/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minecraft Mansave</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/minecraft-mansave/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/minecraft-mansave/</guid><description>Minecraft Mansave: a kamikaze and lifeguards. If the kamikaze dies, he WON! If he&amp;rsquo;s still alive after (by default in my addon) 2 minutes, he lost! This idea was originally invented by McBirken and I ported it to Bedrock as an addon!
This is a simple function pack of McBirken&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Minecraft Manhunt but if I DIE, the Hunters LOOSE&amp;rdquo;, AKA &amp;ldquo;Minecraft Mansave&amp;rdquo; (and yes I&amp;rsquo;m that XXL Steve guy that suggested this name) game.</description></item><item><title>Minecraft, But Gravity Flips Every Minute</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/minecraft-but-gravity-flips-every-minute/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/minecraft-but-gravity-flips-every-minute/</guid><description>Every minute, gravity flips for 30 seconds! You will get levitated in the air! The goal of this challenge is to beat Minecraft (kill the Ender dragon). Play with your friends or alone!
This is a simple function pack of Dream&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Minecraft, but Gravity Flips Every Minute&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; video/plugin.
Also, thanks to CrazeVideos on YouTube for suggesting that!
How to start:
To start the challenge, simply write /function start in the chat!</description></item><item><title>Eating Time!</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/eating-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/eating-time/</guid><description>Eating Time! is an addon that adds decorating entities like a waterjug, salt shaker, plate, mug, etc. It also adds some items like a fork, spoon, ladle and kitchen knife.
Items:
Fork Spoon Kitchen knife Ladle (texture by ilosemypotato) Napkin Bottle &amp;amp; Water bottle To get these items, write /function items in the chat. Or to get an individual item, write /give @s et: and you will see a list of items.</description></item><item><title>Dream's Minecraft Ultimate Tag</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/dreams-minecraft-ultimate-tag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/dreams-minecraft-ultimate-tag/</guid><description>Dream&amp;rsquo;s Ultimate Tag is a function pack of the minigame &amp;ldquo;Minecraft Ultimate Tag&amp;rdquo; by Dream. A random hunter is chosen and has to tag a runner. If the runner(s) survive for 2 minutes, they win! If they don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; they lose.
As this is a function pack/addon, you can put it in any world!
How to start
To start playing, write /function start in the chat. You will get teleported in a random location.</description></item><item><title>French Slap</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/french-slap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/french-slap/</guid><description>French Slap is a game where the goal is to knock the players off the map. Last player alive wins! But this map is in a &amp;ldquo;typically-French&amp;rdquo; theme/style, and with little twists!
Additions:
Baguette - enchanted with Knockback 2, use it to hit players off the map! Cheese Power - right-click on PC or long-tap on mobile to trigger it, and you will get a levitation effect for 1 second! Power-up - it will randomly spawn in the game.</description></item><item><title>No More Scary Cave Sounds</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/no-more-scary-cave-sounds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/no-more-scary-cave-sounds/</guid><description>No More Scary Cave Sounds is a resource pack that will change the cave sounds (yes, they got added in 1.16!) &amp;ldquo;ambient.cave&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;ambient&amp;rdquo; sounds like water lowing in a cave or birds singing.
This resource pack will change the ambient.cave sounds to less terrifying sounds (I hope so!). The cave sounds also play in superflat worlds &amp;amp; servers even though you&amp;rsquo;re not in a cave so that could make your gameplay more &amp;ldquo;ambient&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>A Little Simple Spleef Game</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/spleef/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/spleef/</guid><description>Just a little, simple Spleef game. This map contains 2 arenas; the first with 2 layers and the second with 3 layers, and 2 gamemodes (Classic Spleef &amp;amp; Snowball Spleef).
How to Play:
Your goal is to break the block under the other players to make them fall. At the final layer they will fall to the void and die! Last player alive wins.
Gamemodes:
Classic Spleef: Normal Spleef.
Snowball Spleef: In this gamemode you will have 1 snowball for every block you break.</description></item></channel></rss>