<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on XXL Steve</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on XXL Steve</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 12:02:47 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xxlsteve.net/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>X Minecraft Launcher - the only launcher you need</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/x-minecraft-launcher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 12:02:47 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/x-minecraft-launcher/</guid><description>X Minecraft Launcher : An Open Source Minecraft Launcher with Modern UX. Multi-instancing in a disk efficient way, as well as offline accounts support. Intro
I think we&amp;rsquo;ve all been frustrated because of a new problem with the official Minecraft launcher: crashes, logging in is not working&amp;hellip;
There are so many bugs that an entire article is dedicated for that on the Minecraft help center.
Looking for better solutions, I found the launcher MultiMC which I used for quite a while until I found PolyMC (which is a
fork of MultiMC), then migrated to Prism Launcher because PolyMC got compromised.</description></item><item><title>What is NoxCity?</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/noxcity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:33:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/noxcity/</guid><description>NoxCity was born around 2019, as the original name of NoxTown. NoxTown quickly became NoxCity, and the staff grew very big.
The purpose of the world was to build a city and roleplay in it. It had several addons adding furniture, but also cars and pets. Anyone could join and start building so the city became bigger and bigger.
I tried making a logo. I also worked on an addon for NoxCity which added road blocks and custom music, and made a skin pack for it.</description></item><item><title>What is Ulorium Games?</title><link>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/uloriumgames/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:32:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://xxlsteve.net/blog/uloriumgames/</guid><description>How it started
Ulorium Games was founded by Sam0312 (Sam0312#3846 on discord) around the 4th of may 2020. It was preceded by a few other worlds like one named &amp;ldquo;Plantania&amp;rdquo; for which I had made an addon.
The first build of UloriumGames
I was already friends with him at the time, so I would occasionally hop on and help him with the world.
The rise
More and more people would know about the world, so Sam made a Discord server.</description></item></channel></rss>